<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="449" uniqueCount="365"><si><t>Introduction</t></si><si><t>e3060 || Petshack Project</t></si><si><t>Technology</t></si><si><t>Web App: React, Web Panel &amp; Web Services: React + Python; Database : PostgreSQL</t></si><si><t>Web Panel : Supported Browsers</t></si><si><t>All latest versions of Firefox, Chrome &amp; Safari supported ; Internet Explorer not supported</t></si><si><t>#</t></si><si><t>Module</t></si><si><t>Sub-Module</t></si><si><t>Description</t></si><si><t>Estimation</t></si><si><t>Notes</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Client Comments </t></si><si><t>React</t></si><si><t>Python</t></si><si><t>Country</t></si><si><t>Australia</t></si><si><t>Language</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">English </t></si><si><t>Adding any other languages may require additional effort</t></si><si><t>Currency</t></si><si><t>USD</t></si><si><t>Adding any other currencies may require additional effort</t></si><si><t>Database Design</t></si><si><t>Project Setup</t></si><si><t>User Roles</t></si><si><t>End User</t></si><si><t>Website</t></si><si><t>Super Admin</t></si><si><t>Web Panel</t></si><si><t>Homepage</t></si><si><t>Banner Image</t></si><si><t>Multiple banner image carousel would be shown here. Clicking upon this user would be redirected to merchant's site.</t></si><si><t>Navigation bar</t></si><si><t>Quick buttons to navigate to different pages of the webstie.</t></si><si><t>Company Details</t></si><si><t>The homepage will consist of company details, what solution does company provide to the customers, quick navigation to product details, and any additional information provided by the client.</t></si><si><t>Global Search</t></si><si><t>Search bar to serch the products on the bases of products, brand or categories.</t></si><si><t>Quick Navigation</t></si><si><t>A moving carousel of different for user to quickly navigate to product page.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Animal</t></si><si><t>Based upon animal (Dog, cat, fish, reptile, bird, horse, wildlife, small animals)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Top Brands</t></si><si><t>Based upon brands (Royal Canin, Black Hawk, Hills, Breder's Choice, Advance, Perina Pro Plan, Kong, Greenies, Billes Bowl)</t></si><si><t>Contact Us</t></si><si><t>Contact Us form</t></si><si><t>Compare Page</t></si><si><t>Display product results based on selected category or search input by the user</t></si><si><t>List of products</t></si><si><t>List of product based upon the search result would be shown with pagination, searching and sorting functionality. Following details would be shown per product.</t></si><si><t>Product Image: Label</t></si><si><t>Product Name: Label</t></si><si><t>Lowest Product Price: Label</t></si><si><t>Shipping Price: Label (Based upon lowest price store)</t></si><si><t>Stock Availability: Label (Based upon lowest price store)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Store Name: Label (Based upon lowest price store) </t></si><si><t>Store Logo: Label (Based upon lowest price store)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Go To Store</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user would be redirected to third party store page of the product.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Notify Me (Non logged in user)</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can create an alert for the product price. User need to provide following details to get an alert.</t></si><si><t>First Name: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Last Name: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Email: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Price Drop Below: Numeric Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>An email would be sent to user when product price drops below the specified price by the user.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Notify Me (Logged in user)</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can create an alert for the product price. User can provide price details to get the alert.</t></si><si><t>An email would be sent to user when product price drops below the specified price by the user. Also, user can view the alert triggert on alert panel.</t></si><si><t>Notify would trigger once for the product and then auto expire.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     View Other Stores</t></si><si><t>Dropdown, clicking upon this user can view other details and prices. Per store we would shown following details</t></si><si><t>Product Price: Label</t></si><si><t>Shipping price: Label</t></si><si><t>Stock Availibility: Label</t></si><si><t>Store Name: Label</t></si><si><t>Store Logo: Label</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">          Go To Store</t></si><si><t>Filter By</t></si><si><t>Filter the list of product on different parameters</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Pet Types</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of pet types (e.g., Dog, Cat, etc.)</t></si><si><t>Parameter in filter would be dynamic based upon the scrap data from the store website.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Categories</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of categories (e.g., Clothing, Food, Harnes etc.)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Product Brands</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of product brands (e.g., Royal Canin, Black Hawk, Hills, Breder's Choice etc.)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Life Stage</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of life stage for pets (e.g., Adult, Baby, Senior etc.)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Price Range</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of price range.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Pet Stores</t></si><si><t>User can filter the list of the products on the bases of stores</t></si><si><t>Store added on the admin side would be visible to filter the products data.</t></si><si><t>Sort By</t></si><si><t>Sort the list of the product on different parameters.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Price (High to Low)</t></si><si><t>Product can be sorted on the bases of price (high to low).</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Price (Low to High)</t></si><si><t>Product can be sorted on the bases of price (low to high).</t></si><si><t>Last Price Update</t></si><si><t>Label, last time the price was updated on backend side</t></si><si><t>Blog</t></si><si><t>List of all the blogs posted by the admin would be shown here. Following details would be displayed on this page.</t></si><si><t>Search</t></si><si><t>Textbox, user can search the blog on the bases of title and author name.</t></si><si><t>List of Blogs</t></si><si><t>List of blogs would be shown here with pagination and searching functionality.</t></si><si><t>Blog Image: Label</t></si><si><t>Blog Title: Label</t></si><si><t>Author: Label</t></si><si><t>Publish Date: Label</t></si><si><t>Blog Description: Label (Upto 100 characters)</t></si><si><t>View More</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user would be redirected to blog detailed page.</t></si><si><t>Blog Detailed Page</t></si><si><t>Following details would be shown here.</t></si><si><t>Blog Description: Label</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Share</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this the link for the blog would be copied in the clipboard which can be shared outside the system.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     More from author</t></si><si><t>3-4 cards showcasing blogs published by the author with following details</t></si><si><t>Clicking upon the card user would be redirected to blog detailed page.</t></si><si><t>Chatbot</t></si><si><t>This would be static based chatbot where user can see predefined questions and click upon the question to generate the answers. Following details would be shown on the chatbot.</t></si><si><t>Welcome message</t></si><si><t>As a label</t></si><si><t>Chat</t></si><si><t>Predefined question as button. Clicking upon it answer responses would be generated.</t></si><si><t>User can also ask question and answer would be generated based upon tag matching defined.</t></si><si><t>Fallback message for unknown questions (Static)</t></si><si><t>Restart Chat</t></si><si><t>To clear all the chat and restart.</t></si><si><t>Sign Up</t></si><si><t>First Name</t></si><si><t>Textbox, mandatory field, alphabetic inputs only</t></si><si><t>Last Name</t></si><si><t>Email Address</t></si><si><t>Textbox, mandatory, with email address validation.</t></si><si><t>Password</t></si><si><t>Textbox, mandatory field</t></si><si><t>Must contain at least one uppercase letter, one lowercase letter, one number, one symbol, and be a minimum of 8 characters.</t></si><si><t>Confirm Password</t></si><si><t>Same rules as Password. Must match the Password entered above.</t></si><si><t>Terms &amp; Conditions</t></si><si><t>User must select a checkbox to agree to the Terms &amp; Conditions. A link will be available to open the Terms &amp; Conditions page.</t></si><si><t>Confirm</t></si><si><t>Once all details are entered and valid, the user can submit the form and the account will be created.</t></si><si><t>Account Verification</t></si><si><t>Verification via Email</t></si><si><t>Once the form is submitted, an email with a verification link will be sent to the email address provided by the user</t></si><si><t>The user clicks the link to verify the email and activate the account.</t></si><si><t>Login</t></si><si><t>User can log in by :</t></si><si><t>Email address</t></si><si><t>Textbox, mandatory</t></si><si><t>Forgot Password</t></si><si><t>User can reset the password by :</t></si><si><t>By Email address</t></si><si><t>User will receive an email with a verification link on the verified email address</t></si><si><t>When the user clicks the link, they are taken to a screen where they can enter and confirm a new password.</t></si><si><t>Menu</t></si><si><t>The following options will be shown in the site menu. User can navigate to the various sections from here</t></si><si><t>My Profile</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'My Profile' screen</t></si><si><t>My Alert</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'My Alert' screen</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'Contact Us' screen</t></si><si><t>About Us</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'About Us' screen</t></si><si><t>Terms and Conditions</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'Terms and Conditions' screen</t></si><si><t>Privacy Policy</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'Privacy Policy' screen</t></si><si><t>FAQ</t></si><si><t>This will take the user to the 'FAQ' screen</t></si><si><t>Logout</t></si><si><t>This will log the user out of the site</t></si><si><t>Following page would consist all the alerts generated for the user price alerts. Following details would be displayed here.</t></si><si><t>List of alert</t></si><si><t>All the alerts triggered as per 'Notify Me' request of the user would be shown here. Following details would be displayed here.</t></si><si><t>Static message about price going below the price for which alert was set.</t></si><si><t>Clicking upon the alert user would be redirected to the compare page (and would show product for which alert was triggered).</t></si><si><t>Clear All</t></si><si><t>Button</t></si><si><t>Clicking upon this user can clear all the alert triggered</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Following details would be shown on the profile page. </t></si><si><t>User Details</t></si><si><t>Following details would be shown here</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Profile Picture </t></si><si><t>Initially empty; user can upload from local storage or capture using their device.</t></si><si><t>If no picture is added, the first letter of the first name and the first letter of the last name will be shown as initials (e.g., John Doe → “JD”).</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Email Address</t></si><si><t>Label, view-only, cannot be changed.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     First Name</t></si><si><t>User can change</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Last Name</t></si><si><t>Change Password</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Current Password</t></si><si><t>Textbox</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     New Password</t></si><si><t>Textbox – must contain one uppercase letter, one lowercase letter, one number, one symbol, minimum 8 characters.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Confirm New Password</t></si><si><t>Textbox – same rules as New Password; must match the New Password.</t></si><si><t>About Yourself</t></si><si><t>Textbox; user can enter or edit their bio.</t></si><si><t>Become A Partner</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>User would be redirected to website link.&quot;</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://membership.petshack.au/forpartners</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>&quot;</t></r></si><si><t>Membership</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>User would be redirected to website link.&quot;</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://membership.petshack.au/</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>&quot;</t></r></si><si><t>Content managed from the admin panel; displayed as web content.</t></si><si><t>Fields: Name, Email Address, Notes.

Upon submission, an email is sent to the admin with the details entered by the user.</t></si><si><t>Admin Panel</t></si><si><t>Authentication</t></si><si><t>Login &amp; logout</t></si><si><t>Profile with Reset Password</t></si><si><t>Dashboard</t></si><si><t>Total Users in the system</t></si><si><t>Label with count; when clicked, opens the user management.</t></si><si><t>Total Stores Added</t></si><si><t>Label with count; when clicked, opens the store management</t></si><si><t>Total Blogs Live</t></si><si><t>Label with count; when clicked, open the blog management</t></si><si><t>Total Active Banner</t></si><si><t>Label with count; when clicked, open the banner management</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Last Details Updated </t></si><si><t>Label with count, Time at which last price were updated.</t></si><si><t>User management</t></si><si><t>List of all users in the system</t></si><si><t>End Users</t></si><si><t>End users who have signed up for the platform would show here in a list with pagination, searching &amp; sorting</t></si><si><t>All details provided at account creation are visible.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Actions</t></si><si><t>Admin can activate/deactivate any end user.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Export</t></si><si><t>Admin can export the end users list in an Excel format</t></si><si><t>Store Management</t></si><si><t>Admin can manage and add new store from here. Following details would be shown here.</t></si><si><t>Add Store</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user need to provide the following details to add the store.</t></si><si><t>Store Name: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Store Logo: Imagepicker</t></si><si><t>Store Link: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Store Description: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>List of store</t></si><si><t>List of all the stores added would be shown here with pagination, searching and sorting functionality with following details.</t></si><si><t>Store Link:: Label</t></si><si><t>Store Status: Label (Active, Inactive)</t></si><si><t>Store Added On (Date): Label</t></si><si><t>Last fetch data: Label</t></si><si><t>Actions</t></si><si><t>Following actions can be taken per store.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     View Details</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can view the following details</t></si><si><t>Store Description: Label</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Edit Details</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can edit the details of the store</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Activate / Deactivate</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Button, clicking upon this user can activate/deactivate the store.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Note: </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Deactivating the store would stop the data scrapping for that store.</t></r></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Delete</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can delete the store upon confirmation.</t></si><si><t>Blog Management</t></si><si><t>User can manage and publish the blog from this screen. Following details would be shown here.</t></si><si><t>Add Blog</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user need to provide the following details to add the blog on the website.</t></si><si><t>Blog Title: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Blog Cover Image: Imagepicker, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Blog Author: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Blog Description: This would be a rich textbox editor, Mandatory</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Save as Draft: </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> Button, to save the blog as draft and publish later.</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Publish:</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> Button, to publish the blog live on the website.</t></r></si><si><t>List of Blog</t></si><si><t>List of all the blog published would be shown here with pagination, searching and sorting functionality with following details.</t></si><si><t>Author Name: Label</t></si><si><t>Blog Status: Label (Active, Draft, Not active)</t></si><si><t>Blog Added On (Date): Label</t></si><si><t>Following actions can be taken per blog.</t></si><si><t>Blog Status: Label (LIve, Draft, Not live)</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can edit the details of the blog</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">     Publish / Take Down</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can publish the blog/take down the blog from website.</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can delete the blog upon confirmation.</t></si><si><t>Chatbot Management</t></si><si><t>Admin can manage the chatbot question answer resources from this screen. Following details would be shown here.</t></si><si><t>Add Question</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user need to provide the following details to add the question</t></si><si><t>Question: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Answer: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Tags: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>List of Q/A</t></si><si><t>List of all the Q/A added would be shown here with pagination, searching and sorting functionality with following details.</t></si><si><t>Question: Label</t></si><si><t>Answer: Label</t></si><si><t>Tags: Label</t></si><si><t>Status: Label (Active, Inactive)</t></si><si><t>Q/A Created On (Date): Label</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can view the following details in a modal</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can edit the details.</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can activate/deactivate the Q/A resource for chat.</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can delete the details upon confirmation.</t></si><si><t>Banner Management</t></si><si><t>Admin can manage the banner on the homepage from this screen. Following details would be shown here.</t></si><si><t>Add Banner</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user need to provide the following details to add the banner</t></si><si><t>Banner Name: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Banner Image: Imagepicker, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Redirection Link: Textbox, Mandatory</t></si><si><t>Banner Note: Textbox</t></si><si><t>List of banner</t></si><si><t>List of all the banner added would be shown here with pagination, searching and sorting functionality with following details.</t></si><si><t>Banner Name: Label</t></si><si><t>Banner Image: Label</t></si><si><t>Store Link: Label</t></si><si><t>Banner Note: Label</t></si><si><t>Banner Status: Label (Active, Inactive)</t></si><si><t>Banner Created On (Date): Label</t></si><si><t>Banner Link:: Label</t></si><si><t>Banner Added On (Date): Label</t></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can edit the details of the banner</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Button, clicking upon this user can activate/deactivate the banner.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Note: </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Deactivating the banner would stop the banner been shown on the homepage.</t></r></si><si><t>Button, clicking upon this user can delete the banner details upon confirmation.</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Note</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="Arial"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>: List of all active banner would be shown on the homepage as carousel.</t></r></si><si><t>CMS Management</t></si><si><t>Super admin can add the content for the following pages of the platform.</t></si><si><t>This would be a rich textbox editor.</t></si><si><t>'Contact Us' queries</t></si><si><t>Any queries that the user sent via the 'Contact Us' form will be shown here</t></si><si><t>Queries</t></si><si><t>List with pagination, searching, sorting</t></si><si><t>Admin can view the query, timestamp, and user details.</t></si><si><t>Admin will contact the user outside the system if needed.</t></si><si><t>Once resolved, admin can mark the query as closed.</t></si><si><t>Backend Points</t></si><si><t>Data Scrapping and Normalization</t></si><si><t>Data Scrapping</t></si><si><t>Architect and deploy robust crawlers to ingest pricing and stock data from 50+ Australian retailers every 24 hours.</t></si><si><t>Automated scrapers or data feeds crawl each partner store’s category and product pages on a schedule, extract structured product data using predefined rules, and continuously sync it into the system without manual intervention.</t></si><si><t>Ensure zero-downtime performance and strict adherence to anti-bot measures (proxy management, fingerprinting).</t></si><si><t>Data Normalization</t></si><si><t>This is the core requirement. We need a system that automatically maps disparate retailer data to a single &quot;Master SKU.&quot;</t></si><si><t>The system must intelligently handle variations: e.g., mapping &quot;Royal Canin G.Shepherd 3kg&quot; and &quot;RC German Shepherd Adult 3000g&quot; to the same entity without manual intervention.</t></si><si><t>Must utilize advanced logic (Waterfall matching, GTIN/EAN priority, Vector Embeddings, or NLP attribute extraction) to ensure a very high accuracy. Misleading users with unmatched products is not an option.</t></si><si><t>Notifications</t></si><si><t>Email Notfications</t></si><si><t>User</t></si><si><t>Account created</t></si><si><t>Account verification</t></si><si><t>Query raised via 'Contact Us' form</t></si><si><t>Password reset</t></si><si><t>Price Alert Received</t></si><si><t>Admin</t></si><si><t>Query raised by user, via 'Contact Us' form</t></si><si><t>'Contact Us' query closed</t></si><si><t>Project Deployment</t></si><si><t>Deployment</t></si><si><t>One time deployment on LIVE server only</t></si><si><t>UI / UX Design</t></si><si><t>Logo design hours not included.

Standard design hours had been considered. Please let us know if you have any other specific design requirements.</t></si><si><t>Analysis &amp; Project Management</t></si><si><t>Quality Assurance</t></si><si><t>Efforts may vary if anything is added / updated from mentioned features list</t></si><si><t>The Third-party tools / plugins / APIs will be purchased and provided by client</t></si><si><t>The efforts for deployment are considered for one time deployment on LIVE server only</t></si><si><t>Default email templates will be used, it will require additional effort to create custom email templates</t></si></sst>